I'm sorry.
I seemed to have intruded.
Yes you have, haven't you.
I was making the tour of the house
and I got kind of absorbed
in this little book.
I...
should have gone on
down the corridor I guess
but I made a mistake
and took the wrong turn.
I don't call entering a door
marked private making a mistake.
I call that trespassing.
You gonna prosecute me?
'Cause if you are
I shall defend the action
because there is no sign
on this door saying private.
Oh, yes there is.
I beg your pardon.
No, I beg your pardon,
Ma'am. For intruding, I mean.
-Someone must've taken it down!
-Yes, Ma'am.
Yes, and in England we
only call the Queen Ma'am.
In the United States
we try to make up for
having no royalty
by calling everyone Ma'am.
And now would you be good
enough to put it back?
Put what back?
The notice you remove from the door.
It's there on the floor.
Must've fallen down.
Rubbish, you put it there.
I think I deserve an explanation.
Oh it's quite simple really.
As I had said, I spent a...
wonderful hour going
through your beautiful home.
You mean house, don't you?
You could hardly call a place a home
when people only have to pay two
and six pence to walk all over it.
So, not content with
seeing the public rooms
you wanted to see the private
ones as well, is that it?
Let's just say I was curious to
see the people who live in them.
Well, nowadays, I'm afraid
an Englishman's home is not his castle,
it's his income, and it's unfair
of you to take advantage of it.
Yes, Ma'am. I mean, no Ma'am.
I don't mean no Ma'am...
I just remember not to say Ma'am.
That's all.
Yes, well. Don't
worry about it anymore.
Thank you.
You are Lady Rhyall, aren't you?
Yes.
Well, I'm very glad to meet you.
How do you do.
Yes, you'd sort of have
to be, wouldn't you?
Why?
Well, you're perfect type-casting.
Don't tell me you're
in the film industry.
Hardly, no.
I'm an oil man.
-Oh, you're a millionaire!
-As a matter of fact, I am.
Won't you sit down?
Thank you.
Tell me, why were you so...
why were you so sure
I was a millionaire?
Well, nearly all the
Americans I meet seem to be.
Especially the oily ones.
Well, I hoped you'd be impressed.
As a matter of fact, I am.
Just a little.
Have you been a millionaire
for quite some time?
I guess I have at that.
Tell me,
Why do you think I'm type-casting?
Well you're cool and elegant.
You're at ease,
and...
And what?
And very lovely.
I suppose you're a millionaire because
you insist upon value for money.
I must say you are getting
your half-crown's worth, aren't you?
I'm an American, I say what I think.
And hesitate before you say it.
A Frenchman
would never have hesitated.
And an Englishman?
An Englishman
would never have said it.
You mean an Englishman would never
tell a married woman she was lovely?
No, no, I don't mean that.
It's just that he usually tells
the husband first.
What's the point in that?
Oh, because he knows the
husband will tell the wife.
"Do you know what old George
said to me last night, my dear.
"He said he thought you looked lovely".
I said very lovely.