And so the...
wife is intrigued and...
the next time she's
alone with George
she sees to it that
he tells her himself.
Well, it's an oblique approach
but not a bad one, and...
very effective.
So, I understand.
Well, I don't know your husband.
And my name is not George, it's Charles.
What's yours?
-Hilary.
-Hilary?
That's a boy's name.
You don't look like a boy to me.
Charlies what?
Delacro,
D-E-L-A-C-R-O.
-Oh, sounds French.
-It is, was.
Used to be
Delacroix, C-R-O-I-X.
But...
we Americans are a simple,
straightforward people.
We see an X on the end of
a name and we pronounce it.
My grandfather thought Dela-Quacks
sounded like a duck laying an egg,
so we cut it off.
The X, I mean.
He was born in France. In Tours.
Oh now, isn't that odd.
I had a French grandfather and
he was born in Turenne,
perhaps were cousins?
Oh, I doubt that.
Your grandfather was probably a
nobleman. Mine was a clockmaker.
And now you're a millionaire,
and I'm a mushroom grower.
Oh well, there you are.
That's the way the world wags.
It's a little early to
offer you a cup of tea.
Would you like a drink, or something?
I don't really want one, but...
accepting a drink means
that I'm now your guest,
and not just an intruder,
then, by all means.
Yes, well. Perhaps you'd like
to help yourself.
Alright, thank you.
I imagine it's something
you're quite used to.
Helping yourself, I mean.
Was that a crack or a compliment?
Which do you think it is?
Well, in my country I'd probably
consider it a compliment.
Here it's probably a crack.
And if you don't mind my saying so,
I think that's a pity.
Well, I'm not really
in a position to argue.
The relative value of mushrooms
and oil in the world market today
being so unfairly what it is.
And don't try and turn the tables on me.
I apologize.
It's only that some of
the customs of this country
I find more unusual than others.
-Having no ice in my drink...
-Oh blast!
-I can make you some in two minutes!
-I really don't mind, honestly.
I don't complain until
it actually burns my tongue.
I'm really terribly sorry.
Would you...
like me to fix you a drink?
Fix? You sound as if you're going
to drug me or something.
Sometimes I'm convinced
that the greatest barrier
between our two countries
is the bond of a common language.
Could I...
May I pour you out a drink?
No, thank you.